[Music] The
[âm nhạc]
Buddha is the sun that shines upon people, dispelling the
nước Thế Tôn là mặt trời chiếu soi người
dark night and dispelling the wind of
phá tan đi m đêm u tối gió tan bị tà kiế
suffering. The Buddha, in his form, is the embodiment of wisdom,
khổ đau Đức Thế Tôn dạng hơi trí tuệ
encompassing all three thousand
ngài bao trùm khắp tam
worlds. The Buddha, the compassionate father of all beings, who can
thiên đức thế tôn từ phụ muôn loài ai
save humanity? No one
cứu được nhân loại người An không ai
but the Buddha. Humanity is sinking
ngoài Đức Thế Tôn nhân loại đang chìm
in darkness, protecting us from the suffering of wrong views. The
trong u tối hộ mình ta kiến khổ đầu Đức
Buddha carries the Dharma, always speaking words of wisdom to dispel delusion. May
Thế Tôn mang tranh Pháp luôn lời xó t đi
the month of enlightenment bring joy to
mê lầm dm tháng từ sáng
all beings. May all beings rejoice. May the
tươi mọi chúng sinh ca mừng mọi chúng
Buddha save the world. The Buddha saves the world. The
sinh cầu M Đức Thế Tôn Đức Thế Tôn cứu
Buddha saves the world.
đời đức thế tôn cứu đời
[Music] The
[âm nhạc]
Buddha is the sun that shines upon people,
Đức Thế Tôn là mặt trời chiếu soi người
dispelling the dark night and dispelling the wind of
phá tan đi mang đêm u tối gió tan đi Tà
suffering. The Buddha, in his form, is the embodiment of wisdom,
kiến khổ đau Đức Thế Tôn giạ ngơi trí
encompassing all three thousand
tuệ ngài bao trùm khắp tam
worlds. The Buddha, the compassionate father of all beings, who can
thiên đức thế tôn từ phục muôn loài ai
save humanity? No one
cứu được nhân loại người ấy không ai
but the Buddha. Humanity is sinking
ngoài Đức Thế Tôn nhân loại đang chìm
in darkness, protecting us from the suffering of wrong views. The
trong u Tối vô mình ta kiến khổ đầu Đức
Buddha carries the Dharma, always speaking words of wisdom to dispel delusion. May the month of enlightenment bring joy to
Thế Tôn mang tranh pháp muôn nơi xa t đi
all beings. May all beings rejoice.
tươi mọi chúng sinh cả mừng mọi chúng
May the Buddha
sinh cầu mong Đức Thế Tôn Đức Thế Tôn
save the world. The Buddha, the Buddha, saves the world. The Buddha, the
cứu đời đức thế tôn cứu đời Đức Thế Tôn
self-sacrificing one, who can save humanity?
tự phụ muốn loi ai thếu được nhân loại
That kind of person is none other than the Buddha.
người ấy không ai ngoài Đức Thế Tôn nhân
Humanity is sinking into darkness, ignorance, and
loại đang chìm trong u Tối vô mình t
suffering. The Buddha brings the Dharma, which will last for
kiến khổ đầu đước Thế Tôn mang tranh
eternity, to dispel delusion and ignorance. The Buddha's victory shines
pháp muôn đời xóa tan đi mê lầm dằm
brightly, inspiring all beings. All
tươi mọi chúng sinh ca hừng mọi chúng
beings pray to the Buddha, the Buddha
sinh cầu mong Đức Thế Tôn Đức Thế Tôn
saves the world. The Buddha saves the world.
cứu đời I Đức Thế Tôn cứu đời
[music]
[âm nhạc]
is I
được I